A Guide to the Fillmore Norfleet Papers, 1940-1987
Library of Virginia
- Series IV. Printed materials., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 19-21)
  - Suffolk Citizens: Their Lots and Lives [Ra-Yar] (Box 20, Folder 612)
  - Suffolk Citizens: Their Lots and Lives, Complete List of Biographies [A-Def] (Box 20, Folder 613)
  - Suffolk Citizens: Their Lots and Lives, Complete List of Biographies [Dri-Mas] (Box 20, Folder 614)
  - Suffolk Citizens: Their Lots and Lives, Complete List of Biographies [McA-Ric] (Box 20, Folder 615)
  - Suffolk Citizens: Their Lots and Lives, Complete List of Biographies [Rid-Smi] (Box 20, Folder 616)
  - Suffolk Citizens: Their Lots and Lives, Complete List of Biographies [Spa-Yar] (Box 20, Folder 617)
  - Suffolk Citizens: Their Lots and Lives, Complete List of Biographies [carbon of typescript, A-R] (Box 20, Folder 618)
  - Suffolk in Virginia [Rough Draft, Corrections pp. 1-114] (Box 20, Folder 619)
  - Suffolk in Virginia [pp. 115-Index] (Box 20, Folder 620)
  - Suffolk in Virginia [notes] (Box 20, Folder 621)
  - Suffolk in Virginia [notes for plates 1,2] (Box 20, Folder 622)
  - Suffolk in Virginia [Bibliography and 3 annotated copies] (Box 20, Folder 623)
  - 1810 Nansemond Co. Census [1815 Tax List, annotated] (Box 21, Folder 624)
  - The Virginia Genealogist [Vol. 11, No. 3 pp. 99-103; Vol. 11, No. 4 pp. 160-166; Vol. 26 No. 2; Vol. 27 No. 4 pt. 2, annotated] (Box 21, Folder 625)
- Series V. Published Works., Extent: 1 box. (Box 21)
  Annotated works are distinguished by (a).
  - The Abridged Compendium of American Genealogy, Frederick A. Virkus, Vol. 1 (a) (Box 21)
  - A Proclamation for Setting the Plantation of Virginia, 1625 (Box 21)
  - Fragment of a French history book (Box 21)
  - A la memoire de Louis Deroche (1915-1975) (Box 21)
  - Iron Works at Tuball, Lester J Cappon (Box 21)
  - Excavations at Tutler's Neck, Ivor Noel Hume (Box 21)
  - Excavations at Clay Bank, Ivor Noel Hume (Box 21)
  - Odom-Riddick Reunion, 23 June 1968 (Box 21)
  - Genealogy Kilby, Tynes, Riddick, Smith, Glazebrook, Etc., 2 copies (a) (Box 21)
  - Barraud the Story of a Family, E. M. Barraud (a) (Box 21)
  - An Allen Lineage c. 1500-1979, Allen Belden (a) (Box 21)
  - Family and Friends Pine Town NC, 1893-1918, Elizabeth Parker Roberts (a) (Box 21)
  - A Record of Farms and Their Owners in Lower Parish of Nansemond Co., Virginia, William Turner Jordan (a) (Box 21)
  - Norfolk County, Virginia Revolutionary War and War of 1812 Applications for Pensions, Bounty Land Warrants and Heirs of Deceased Prisoners, Elizabeth B. Wingo (a) (Box 21)
  - Marriages of Sussex County, Virginia, 1754-1810, Catherine L. Knorr (a) (Box 21)
  - Marriages of Surry County, Virginia, 1768-1825, Catherine L. Knorr (a) (Box 21)
  - Marriages of Southampton County, Virginia, 1750-1810, Catherine L. Knorr (a) (Box 21)
  - Marriages of Norfolk County, VA 1788, 1793-1817, Elizabeth B. Wingo (Box 21)
  - Marriages of Isle of Wight County, Virginia, 1628-1800, Blanche Adams-Chapman(a) (Box 21)
  - Somerton Meeting, Elizabeth Hare Lasley (Box 21)
  - Vestry Book of Elizabeth River Parish, 1749-61, Alice Granbery Walter (Box 21)
  - Diary of Mrs. William Thornton (a) (Box 21)
  - Bible Records of Gates County, NC (Box 21)
- Series VI. Photographs., Extent: 1 box. (Box 22)
  There is a collection of photographs and negatives in the Fillmore Norfleet Papers. Some of the items were used in his publications, others were sent to him by various correspondents. Those photographs of historical significance have been separated from the correspondence and filed separately. They are alphabetically arranged by the name of the subject. Every attempt was made to identify and label the photographs. In some instances the correspondent wrote on the back of the picture. Some items, not otherwise identified, have been foldered and labeled.
  - Photographs, A-H (Box 22, Folder 626)
  - Photographs, J-W, unidentified (Box 22, Folder 627)